vietvoice.net 2002-06-04

# .:: VIETVOICE ENTERTAINMENT ::.

****.:: Privacy Statement for VietVoice Entertainment ::.****

VietVoice Entertainment has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: VietVoice Entertainment. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

This site contains links to other sites. **VietVoice Entertainment** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program. 

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@vietvoice.net](mailto:webmaster@vietvoice.net)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Email [webmaster@vietvoice.net](mailto:webmaster@vietvoice.net)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  VietVoice Entertainment webmaster@vietvoice.net
